masnsports.com 2019-05-11

# MASN News & Information - MASNsports.com

_Last Updated: September 1, 2018_

This Privacy Policy applies to your access and use of the MASN websites, mobile applications, and other online programs (“MASN Site”). By accessing or using any of the MASN Site, you agree that you have read and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you don’t agree, please do not use any of the MASN Site.

When you use any of the MASN Site, we may collect information about you and we may share some of all of that information with third parties in certain circumstances. This Privacy Policy will give you more details and information about such collection, use and sharing.

Our business is located in the United States. Our online privacy practices are governed by the laws of the United States and the State of Maryland. By using any of the MASN Site, you understand and agree that any information you submit or is gathered about you will be transmitted to and stored in the United States. You further consent to the use and disclosure of that information accordance with applicable U.S. Federal and State laws and with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may be updated and changed from time to time. Please check periodically for changes. See additional details in the Changes/Updates section below. 

List of topics:  
* Information We Collect  
* How We Use Information  
* Use or Sharing of Personal Information  
* Use or Sharing of Non-Personal Information  
* Cookies, Web Beacons and Online Advertising  
* Social Networking and Third-Party Sites  
* California Residents  
* Children  
* Security  
* Retention of Information  
* Changes/Updates

 **Information We Collect**  
Personal Information. The types of information we collect that identify you or relate to you as an individual (“Personal Information”) may include things such as the following:  
1\. Name, date of birth, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, username and password (for account administration), when you supply this information voluntarily  
2\. Device ID, including IP address, which are automatically collected and, while they don’t identify you as an individual, they do identify a particular computer or mobile device   
3\. Geolocation (if you consent to this function)  
4\. Financial account information and other payment information (that you submit to us for order processing)  
5\. Additional Personal Information you may submit as necessary for the administration of particular promotional events, such as sweepstakes or contests

Non-Personal Information. Other types of data will also be collected periodically, such as:  
1\. Type of browser and operating system, mobile application usage data, and aggregated information such as “click stream” information which means entry and exit points (including referring URLs or domains), traffic statistics, page views, and impressions, all of which are collected automatically  
2\. Demographic information you choose to submit and which we may combine on an anonymous basis with similar information from other users  
3\. Information collected through cookies, web beacons, pixel tags and other technologies described in more detail later in the Cookies and Web Beacons section of this Privacy Policy  
4\. Device Information - Device type, OS, and identifier

**How We Use Information**  
We may use Personal Information about you for purposes described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed to you through the MASN Site. This includes the following:  
1\. Process and manage your account and your purchase and use of our products and services  
2\. Respond to your inquiries or requests, and to post your comments or statements on message boards or in our online forums  
3\. Create and deliver personalized promotions based on your purchases and other interactions with us  
4\. Send you communications about offerings from MASN and our affiliated companies  
5\. Improve our online services, including to perform data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, identify usage trends, determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and to operate and expand our business activities

 **Use or Sharing of Personal Information**  
Except as set forth below, we will not knowingly disclose your Personal Information to anyone outside of MASN or our affiliated companies (collectively “MASN”):

* To Perform Services For You We may disclose your Personal Information to third-party service providers to provide us with services such as payment processing, website hosting, professional services, including information technology services and related infrastructure, customer service, e-mail delivery, auditing and other similar services necessary to the MASN Site and services you request.

* Corporate Transactions or Events We may disclose your information to a third party in connection with a corporate reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock, including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings.

* Compliance with Law We may use or disclose your Personal Information as we deem necessary or appropriate: (1) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (2) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (3) to comply with subpoenas and other legal processes; (4) to pursue available remedies or limit damages we may sustain; (5) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliated companies; (6) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of MASN or others; and (7) to enforce our terms and conditions.

* Third Party Marketing If you opt-in to receive marketing communications from third parties, we may, from time to time, share the information you provide to us with a few carefully selected third party marketing partners that we believe offer products or services that may be of interest to you. If you would like us to stop providing your information to our third-party marketing partners, you may opt-out by emailing us at info@masnstudios.com or sending a letter to MASN, 333 W. Camden Street, Baltimore, MD 21201.  
Use or Sharing of Non-Personal Information  
Non-personal information may be used for any purpose not prohibited by law. For example, we may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all information that does not identify an individual (or that has been modified to remove individual identification).

 **Cookies, Web Beacons and Online Advertising**

* What Are Cookies? MASN and its agents use small text files called cookies, (collectively, “Cookies”). Cookies are small pieces of data that we and our agents place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies are not themselves personally identifiable, but may be linked to Personal Information that you provide to us through your online interaction with us. A Cookie will typically contain the name of the domain (internet location) from which the Cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the Cookie (i.e. when does it expire), and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

* Types of Cookies  
Each cookie performs one or more of the following functions:   
(a) Essential Cookies: These first party cookies allow you to use a feature of the MASN Site, such as to stay logged in or make purchase.  
(b) Analytics Cookies: These can be first party or third party cookies. Such cookies track information about how the MASN Site are used so MASN can make improvements and report on our performance. MASN may also use such cookies to test new ads or features.  
(c) Preference Cookies: These first party cookies store your MASN Site preferences.   
(d) Ad Targeting Cookies: These third party cookies (also called “behavioral” or “targeted” advertising) are placed by advertising platforms or networks to deliver ads and track performance or to deliver ads based upon your activities. 

* How We Use Cookies We use Cookies so that we can improve your online experience - for example, by remembering you when you come back to visit us, and making the content you see more relevant to you. Cookies also enable us to track online purchases made through the MASN Site.

* Your Control of Cookies Web browsers allow some control of most Cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about Cookies, including how to see what Cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. Please understand, however, if you disable Cookies, some features of the MASN Site may not work as well (or at all) for you.

* Online Advertising We use Cookies and other technologies, such as pixel tags, web beacons, and clear GIF files, to help manage our online advertising program. These technologies may enable us (or third party advertising services we work with) to learn which advertisements bring users to the MASN Site. They also may enable us (or third-party advertising services we work with) to track the actions of users online over time and across different web sites or platforms to measure statistics of our marketing efforts, and to deliver electronic advertisements that may be more relevant to individual consumers and that will improve the consumer experience. For information about how tracking works for online advertising purposes, and what happens when you elect a do-not-track option, visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. In addition, some third party businesses may provide a mechanism to opt-out of their technology. For more information about the opt-out process, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website, available at: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. At this time, the MASN Site are not able to respond to do-not-track requests from browsers. 

* Analytics

We also use third-party analytics such as Google Analytics to gather and analyze anonymous user information. Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), to collect information about use of the MASN Site. Google may use cookies to collect information about your purchase history, the content you view, what websites you visit immediately prior to and after visiting the MASN Site, and your system information and geographic information. The information generated by the Google cookies about your use of the MASN Site will be transmitted to and stored by Google. The information collected by Google allows us to analyze the use of the MASN Site, but does not identify you.

**Social Networking And Third Party Sites  
**  
When you sign in or link to the MASN Site through any social networking service, any information you supply (or have supplied) to us becomes subject to the privacy policy of that social network/service. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices of such networks or services. You should consult the privacy policy of such networks/services. If you post information in a public forum it becomes public information. In addition, we may disclose your Personal Information in order to identify you to anyone to whom you send communications through the MASN Site. The MASN Site may provide links to other sites or services. If you use such other sites or services, check their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other site or service.

 **California Residents  
**  
Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, also known as the “Shine the Light Law,” any of our users who are California residents are entitled to request and receive once a year, free of charge, a notice from us describing what categories of personal customer information (if any) we shared with third parties or corporate affiliates for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. If applicable, the notice will identify the categories of information shared, the names and addresses of the third parties and affiliates with which information was shared. If you are a California resident and would like to request a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: MASN, Inc., 333 W. Camden Street, Baltimore, MD 21201. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response.

 **Children  
**  
The MASN Site are not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If we learn that we have obtained any personally identifiable information about a child under age 13, we will delete that information.

 **Security  
**  
We strive to use reasonable safeguards to help prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of Personal Information provided or collected through the MASN Site. However, no system is perfect or can guarantee that unauthorized access or theft might not occur.

 **Retention of Information  
**  
Following termination or deactivation of any user account you may create, unless you request that your information be deleted by contacting us, we may retain your information for back-up, archival, legal and audit purposes, and to reactivate your account upon your request. In addition, we may retain and continue to use indefinitely all information contained in your communications to other users of the MASN Site posted to public or semi-public areas of the MASN Site after termination or deactivation of your user account.

 **Changes and Updates  
**  
We will notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy by posting the amended terms on the MASN Site and providing any advance notice required by law. If you have provided us with your email address, we will also notify you of material changes to this Privacy Policy that affect your substantive rights by sending an email before the effective date of such changes to the email address you most recently provided to us. We encourage you to keep the email address you provide to us current, and to promptly notify us of any changes to your email address, so that you may receive any notices we send to you regarding material changes to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the new terms, you should stop using the MASN Site and services. Otherwise, the new terms will take effect on the date listed in the notice we provide.
